A Guide to the Papers of the University Librarian, University of Virginia
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Papers of the University Librarian, University of Virginia
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
RG-12/1/1.101
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Box 15 is restricted.
Acquisition Information
These papers were an archival transfer from Alderman Library through Margaret Peak, Special Projects Manager, on February 18, 2010.
Scope and Content
This collection consists of the papers of the University Librarian, including subject files, library funds reports, personnel records, committee files, etc. ca. 1967–1981, 12,600 items (14 cubics and one Hollinger box, ca. 17.5 linear feet).
Arrangement
The papers are arranged in four series: Series I: General Files (A-Z), arranged alphabetically (Cubics 1-9); Series II: Miscellaneous Files (Cubics 9-10); Series III: Bound Library Funds Reports (Cubics 11-12); and Series IV: Personnel Records, including one restricted box (Cubics 13-14, and Box 15)
Contents List
- Series I: General Files (A-Z)
  - 1967-1973 Area Collections Department (Box-folder 1:1)
  - 1974-1976 Area Collections Department (Box-folder 1:2)
  - 1977-1979 Area Collections Department (Box-folder 1:3)
  - 1970-1976 Art Department (Box-folder 1:4)
  - 1977 Asian Studies, Committee on (Box-folder 1:5)
  - 1980-1981 Associates of the University of Virginia Library (Box-folder 1:6)
  - 1977-1979 Associates of the University of Virginia Library (Box-folder 1:7)
  - 1975-1976 Associates of the University of Virginia Library (Box-folder 1:8)
  - 1968-1973 Athletic Department (Box-folder 1:9)
  - 1979-1980 Audiovisual (Box-folder 1:10)
  - 1981-1982 Auditors (Box-folder 1:11)
  - 1978-1979 B Miscellaneous (Box-folder 1:12)
  - 1977-1982 Barrett Library (Box-folder 1:13)
  - 1973-1978 Barrett Fund (Box-folder 1:14)
  - 1968-1970 Bibliographic Records Services Department (Box-folder 1:15)
  - 1971-1975 Bibliographic Records Services Department (Box-folder 1:16)
  - 1976-1978 Bibliographic Records Services Department (Box-folder 1:17)
  - 1979-1980 Bibliographic Records Services Department (Box-folder 1:18)
  - 1981 Bibliographic Records Services Department (Box-folder 1:19)
  - 1982 Bibliographic Records Services Department (Box-folder 1:20)
  - 1978 Bibliographic Records Services Department-Future of the Card Catalogue (Box-folder 1:21)
  - 1979 Bibliographic Records Services Department-Future of the Card Catalogue (Box-folder 1:22)
  - 1975-1979 Bibliographical Society of the University of Virginia (Box-folder 2:1)
  - 1976-1979 Bibliographical Society of the University of Virginia (Box-folder 2:2)
  - 1975-1979 Board of Alderman (Box-folder 2:3)
  - 1975-1982 Binding (Box-folder 2:4)
  - 1966-1980 Birdwood (Box-folder 2:5)
  - 1976-1982 Board of Visitors (Box-folder 2:6)
  - 1977-1982 Borges, Jorge Luis Collection (Box-folder 2:7)
  - 1975-1978 Buckley Amendment (Box-folder 2:8)
  - 1970-1979 Business Services (Box-folder 2:9)
  - 1969-1982 Byrd Papers (Box-folder 2:10)
  - 1976 C. Miscellaneous (Box-folder 2:11)
  - 1981 Calendar (Box-folder 2:12)
  - 1973-1977 Canadian Materials (Box-folder 2:13)
  - 1969-1979 Capital Outlay (Box-folder 2:14)
  - 1967-1979 Center for Research Libraries (Box-folder 2:15)
  - 1975-1976 Center for Research Libraries Board Meetings (Box-folder 2:16)
  - 1974-1977 Center for Research Libraries Minutes (Box-folder 2:17)
  - 1958-1970 Circulation Department (Box-folder 2:18)
  - 1971 Circulation Department (Box-folder 2:19)
  - 1972-1973 Circulation Department (Box-folder 2:20)
  - 1974 Circulation Department (Box-folder 2:21)
  - 1975 Circulation Department (Box-folder 2:22)
  - 1976-1979 Circulation Department (Box-folder 2:23)
  - 1969-1978 Classical Studies Department (Box-folder 2:24)
  - 1969-1976 Clapp-Jordan Formula (Box-folder 2:25)
  - 1970-1973 Clemons Library (Box-folder 2:26)
  - 1974 Clemons Library (Box-folder 2:27)
  - 1975-1977 Clemons Library (Box-folder 2:28)
  - 1978 Clemons Library (Box-folder 2:29)
  - 1979 Clemons Library (Box-folder 2:30)
  - 1967-1971 Collection Development Department (Box-folder 2:31)
  - 1971-1972 Collection Development Department (Box-folder 3:1)
  - 1973-1974 Collection Development Department (Box-folder 3:2)
  - 1975-1976 Collection Development Department (Box-folder 3:3)
  - 1977-1979 Collection Development Department (Box-folder 3:4)
  - 1968-1975 Collection Development - Acquisitions: Bibliography (Box-folder 3:5)
  - 1969 Collection Development - Acquisition Procedures-Notes on Study made (Box-folder 3:6)
  - 1970-1975 Collection Development - Approval Order Plans (Box-folder 3:7)
  - 1976-1976 Collection Development - Bibliography (Box-folder 3:8)
  - 1971 Collection Development-Gift and Exchange (Box-folder 3:9)
  - 1976-1979 Colonnade Club (Box-folder 3:10)
  - 1975-1979 Comptroller (Box-folder 3:11)
  - 1974-1975 Computing Activities (Box-folder 3:12)
  - 1976-1977 Computing Activities (Box-folder 3:13)
  - 1978 Computing Activities (Box-folder 3:14)
  - 1979 Computing Activities (Box-folder 3:15)
  - 1978-1979 Copyright (Box-folder 3:16)
  - 1970-1979 Departmental Libraries-Biology/Psychology (Box-folder 3:17)
  - 1972-1979 Departmental Libraries-Education (Box-folder 3:18)
  - 1967-1974 Departmental Libraries-Engineering (Box-folder 3:19)
  - 1975 Departmental Libraries-Engineering (Box-folder 3:20)
  - 1968-1975 Departmental Libraries-Fiske Kimball Fine Arts (Box-folder 3:21)
  - 1968-1979 Departmental Libraries-Graduate Business [Darden] (Box-folder 3:22)
  - 1967-1969 Departmental Libraries-Health Sciences (Box-folder 3:23)
  - 1970-1975 Departmental Libraries-Health Sciences (Box-folder 3:24)
  - 1976-1979 Departmental Libraries-Health Sciences (Box-folder 3:25)
  - 1968-1978 Departmental Libraries-Law Library (Box-folder 4:1)
  - 1968-1976 Departmental Libraries-Music Library (Box-folder 4:2)
  - 1977 Departmental Libraries-Music Library (Box-folder 4:3)
  - 1978-1979 Departmental Libraries-Music Library (Box-folder 4:4)
  - 1979-1982 Departmental Libraries-Nursing (Box-folder 4:5)
  - 1948-1978 Departmental Libraries-Philosophy (Box-folder 4:6)
  - 1975-1979 Departmental Representatives (Box-folder 4:7)
  - 1968-1969 Directors' Council (Box-folder 4:8)
  - 1970 Directors' Council (Box-folder 4:9)
  - 1971 Directors' Council (10 4:10)
  - 1972 Directors' Council (Box-folder 4:11)
  - 1973 Directors' Council (Box-folder 4:12)
  - 1974 Directors' Council (13 4:13)
  - 1975 Directors' Council (Box-folder 4:14)
  - 1976 Directors' Council (Box-folder 4:15)
  - 1977 Directors' Council Minutes (16 4:16)
  - 1978 Directors' Council Minutes (Box-folder 4:17)
  - 1970 Directors Work Session-Services to Science Libraries (Box-folder 4:18)
  - 1970 Directors Work Session - Umlauts (Box-folder 4:19)
  - 1969-1976 Economics Department (Box-folder 4:20)
  - 1976-1979 Emergency Procedures (Box-folder 4:21)
  - 1976-1979 Faculty of Arts and Sciences (Box-folder 4:22)
  - 1970-1976 Faculty of Arts and Sciences Budget Committee (Box-folder 4:23)
  - 1970-1976 Faculty of Arts and Sciences -Bylaws (Box-folder 4:24)
  - 1976-1977 Faculty of Arts and Sciences -Steering Committee (Box-folder 4:25)
  - 1971-1977 Faculty Appointments (Reports to Journals) (Box-folder 4:26)
  - 1968-1982 Faculty Data (Box-folder 4:27)
  - 1970-1979 Faculty Procedures (Box-folder 4:28)
  - 1978-1979 Faculty Status (Box-folder 4:29)
  - 1963-1977 Faculty Status (Box-folder 4:30)
  - 1978 Faculty Status-Topics (Box-folder 5:1)
  - 1968-1979 Institutional Analysis (Mr. Frank Lankford) (Box-folder 5:2)
  - 1970-1979 Insurance (Box-folder 5:3)
  - 1973-1980 Library Assistant Committee (Box-folder 5:4)
  - 1960-1976 Library Expenditures (Box-folder 5:5)
  - 1976-1979 Library Hours (Box-folder 5:6)
  - 1961 Library Statistics (Box-folder 5:7)
  - 1962 Library Statistics (Box-folder 5:8)
  - 1963 Library Statistics (Box-folder 5:9)
  - 1965 Library Statistics (Box-folder 5:10)
  - 1966 Library Statistics (Box-folder 5:11)
  - 1967 Library Statistics (Box-folder 5:12)
  - 1968 Library Statistics (Box-folder 5:13)
  - 1969–1970 Library Statistics (Box-folder 5:14)
  - 1970-1971 Library Statistics (Box-folder 5:15)
  - 1971-1972 Library Statistics (Box-folder 5:16)
  - 1972-1973 Library Statistics (Box-folder 5:17)
  - 1974-1975 Library Statistics (Box-folder 5:18)
  - 1976-1979 Library Statistics (Box-folder 5:19)
  - 1969-1978 Library Use (Box-folder 5:20)
  - 1977 Lomb Collection (Box-folder 5:21)
  - 1967-1971 Manuscripts Department (Box-folder 5:22)
  - 1972-1973 Manuscripts Department (Box-folder 6:1)
  - 1974-1975 Manuscripts Department (Box-folder 6:2)
  - 1976-1977 Manuscripts Department (Box-folder 6:3)
  - 1978-1979 Manuscripts Department (Box-folder 6:4)
  - 1968-1970 President's Office (Box-folder 6:5)
  - 1970-1971 President's Office (Box-folder 6:6)
  - 1971-1972 President's Office (Box-folder 6:7)
  - 1972-1973 President's Office (Box-folder 6:8)
  - 1974-1975 President's Office (Box-folder 6:9)
  - 1966-1972 Provost (Box-folder 6:10)
  - 1973-1974 Provost (Box-folder 6:11)
  - 1976-1981 Provost (Box-folder 6:12)
  - 1968-1972 Public Documents (Box-folder 6:13)
  - 1973-1979 Public Documents (Box-folder 6:14)
  - 1980 Public Documents (Box-folder 6:15)
  - 1977-1980 Public Law 480 (Box-folder 6:16)
  - 1977-1979 Faculty Research (Box-folder 6:17)
  - 1976 Questionnaires (Box-folder 6:18)
  - 1977 Questionnaires (Box-folder 6:19)
  - 1978-1979 Questionnaires (Box-folder 6:20)
  - 1967-1972 Reference Department (Box-folder 7:1)
  - 1973-1974 Reference Department (Box-folder 7:2)
  - 1975-1979 Reference Department (Box-folder 7:3)
  - 1974 Science and Technology Information Center (Box-folder 7:4)
  - 1975-1976 Science and Technology Information Center (Box-folder 7:5)
  - 1977-1979 Science and Technology Information Center (Box-folder 7:6)
  - 1966-1967 Science and Technology Information Center (Box-folder 7:7)
  - 1968 Science and Technology Information Center (Box-folder 7:8)
  - 1969 Science and Technology Information Center (Box-folder 7:9)
  - 1970 Science and Technology Information Center (Box-folder 7:10)
  - 1971 Science and Technology Information Center (Box-folder 7:11)
  - 1972 Science and Technology Information Center (Box-folder 7:12)
  - 1973 Science and Technology Information Center (Box-folder 7:13)
  - 1975 Science and Technology Search Service (Box-folder 7:14)
  - 1974-1977 Science Library Advisory Committee (Box-folder 7:15)
  - 1975-1980 Security (Box-folder 7:16)
  - 1974-1979 Self-Study (Box-folder 7:17)
  - 1975-1981 Serials Section (Box-folder 7:18)
  - 1977 Shelflist (Box-folder 7:19)
  - 1978 Shelflist (Box-folder 7:20)
  - 1979 Shelflist (Box-folder 7:21)
  - 1978 Signs (Box-folder 7:22)
  - 1975-1977 Slavic Languages and Literatures (Box-folder 7:23)
  - 1970-1977 Sociology and Anthropology Departments (Box-folder 7:24)
  - 1975 Solinet (Box-folder 7:25)
  - 1976 Solinet (Box-folder 7:26)
  - 1977-1980 Solinet (Box-folder 7:27)
  - 1970-1978 South Asia Area Program (Box-folder 8:1)
  - 1974-1979 Southeastern Library Association (Box-folder 8:2)
  - 1978 Southeastern Library Association - Solar Energy (Box-folder 8:3)
  - 1971-1975 Southeastern Library Association-Task Force on Interstate Cooperation (Box-folder 8:4)
  - 1976-1977 Southern Association of Colleges and Schools (Box-folder 8:5)
  - 1968-1974 Space Projections-Alderman Library (Box-folder 8:6)
  - 1975-1979 Space Projections-Alderman Library (7 8:7)
  - 1971-1975 Spanish, Italian and Portugueses, Department of (Box-folder 8:8)
  - 1967-1979 Special Libraries Association (Box-folder 8:9)
  - 1975-1979 Sponsored Programs (Box-folder 8:10)
  - 1973-1978 Staff Association (Box-folder 8:11)
  - 1979 Staff Members (Lists) (Box-folder 8:12)
  - 1971-1975 State Council of Higher Education in Virginia (Box-folder 8:13)
  - 1976 State Council of Higher Education in Virginia (Box-folder 8:14)
  - 1977-1980 State Council of Higher Education in Virginia (Box-folder 8:15)
  - 1982-1985 Statistics-Association of Research Libraries (booklets)
  - 1967-1968 Statistics (Virginia State Library, University of Virginia, Department of Housing, Education and Welfare) (Box-folder 8:16)
  - 1975-1979 Storage Center (Box-folder 8:17)
  - 1975-1977 Student Affairs (Box-folder 8:18)
  - 1977 Student Council (Box-folder 8:19)
  - 1975-1976 T Miscellaneous (Box-folder 8:20)
  - 1976-1979 Telephones (Box-folder 8:21)
  - 1965-1979 Thefts (Box-folder 8:22)
  - 1975-1979 Thomas Jefferson Memorial Foundation (Box-folder 8:23)
  - 1976-1978 Title II (Box-folder 8:24)
  - 1979 Title II (Box-folder 8:25)
  - 1975-1979 Travel (Box-folder 8:26)
  - 1976-1979 Travel Fund Allocations (Box-folder 8:27)
  - 1976-1978 Treasurer (Box-folder 8:28)
  - 1972-1976 TWX (Box-folder 8:29)
  - 1969-1979 U Miscellaneous (Box-folder 8:30)
  - 1975-1979 United Way (Box-folder 8:31)
  - 1974-1977 University Archivist (Box-folder 8:32)
  - 1971-1975 Office of University Auditor (Box-folder 8:33)
  - 1976 University Center in Virginia (Box-folder 8:34)
  - 1967-1970 University Library Committee (Box-folder 9:1)
  - 1971-1973 University Library Committee (Box-folder 9:2)
  - 1974-1976 University Library Committee (Box-folder 9:3)
  - 1977-1979 University Library Committee (Box-folder 9:4)
  - 1974-1979 University Library Committee -Minutes (Box-folder 9:5)
  - 1967-1978 University Library Committee -Sub-Committee on Collection Development Policies (Box-folder 9:6)
  - 1973-1982 University Microfilms (Box-folder 9:7)
  - 1974-1977 University Police (Box-folder 9:8)
  - 1971-1979 The University Register (Box-folder 9:9)
  - 1967-1977 University of Virginia Press (Box-folder 9:10)
  - 1975-1979 V Miscellaneous (Box-folder 9:11)
  - 1969-1979 Virginia Commonwealth University (Box-folder 9:12)
  - 1978-1979 Virginia Governor's Conference on Library and Information Services (Box-folder 9:13)
  - 1976-1979 Virginia Library Association (Box-folder 9:14)
  - 1975-1983 Virginia State Library (Box-folder 9:15)
  - 1975-1978 W. Miscellaneous (Box-folder 9:16)
  - 1974-1979 Weedon Foundation (Box-folder 9:17)
  - 1968-1973 XYZ Miscellaneous (Box-folder 9:18)
- Series II: Miscellaneous Files
  - 1983-1984 Acquisitions System - INNOVAQ-Contract and Financing (Box-folder 9:19)
  - 1983 Acquisitions System-Feasibility and Selection (Box-folder 9:20)
  - 1983 Acquisitions System-Proposals which were rejected (Box-folder 9:21)
  - 1971-1979 American Council on Education (Box-folder 9:22)
  - 1977-1980 Association of Souteastern Research Libraries-Special Conference (Box-folder 9:23)
  - 1979-1980 Automation-APR Approvals (Box-folder 9:24)
  - 1981-1983 Automation-APR Approvals (Box-folder 9:25)
  - 1981-1984 Automation-Circulation System (Box-folder 9:26)
  - 1983 Automation-Procurement Forms, Contract Lists, etc. (Box-folder 9:27)
  - 1967-1979 Automation-University of Virginia Library-Misc. (Box-folder 9:28)
  - 1980-1987 Automation-University of Virginia Library-Misc. (Box-folder 9:29)
  - 1976 Bicentennial (Box-folder 9:30)
  - 1983-1985 Billings, Elden E. (Box-folder 9:31)
  - 1977-1983 Binding (Box-folder 9:32)
  - 1976-1983 Bishko, Julian (Box-folder 9:33)
  - 1968-1979 Blackwell's-London, England (Box-folder 9:34)
  - 1967-1977 California, University of (Box-folder 9:35)
  - 1976 Central Intelligence Agency (Box-folder 9:36)
  - 1976 Chicago-Cataloging / Circulation System (Box-folder 9:37)
  - 1957-1979 Childs, J. Rives (Box-folder 9:38)
  - 1980-1983 The Computer Company - Contract (Box-folder 9:39)
  - 1982-1983 The Computer Company - Contract (Box-folder 9:40)
  - 1983-1985 The Computer Company - Contract (Box-folder 10:1)
  - 1985-1986 The Computer Company - Contract (Box-folder 10:2)
  - 1986-1988 The Computer Company - Contract (Box-folder 10:3)
  - 1980-1982 The Computer Company - Correspondence (Box-folder 10:4)
  - 1983-1988 The Computer Company - Correspondence (Box-folder 10:5)
  - 1981-1984 The Computer Company - Expenditures (Box-folder 10:6)
  - 1970-1977 Degree Programs (Box-folder 10:7)
  - 1975-1979 Devan, Christopher B. (Box-folder 10:8)
  - 1974-1981 The Directory (Box-folder 10:9)
  - 1967-1976 Door Check (Box-folder 10:10)
  - 1964-1979 Dos Passos, John (Box-folder 10:11)
  - 1979 Drake, Mrs. John B. (Box-folder 10:12)
  - 1973-1981 DuPont Fellowships (Box-folder 10:13)
  - 1975-1981 Energy Commission (Box-folder 10:14)
  - 1968-1975 Federal Executive Institute (Box-folder 10:15)
  - 1969-1976 Federal Library Committee (Library of Congress) (Box-folder 10:16)
  - 1973-1976 Founder's Day (Box-folder 10:17)
  - 1972-1978 Julien Green (Box-folder 10:18)
  - 1983-1984 Holden, Matthew (Box-folder 10:19)
  - 1968-1976 Housing Division (Box-folder 10:20)
  - 1975-1980 Jeffress, Robert M. (Box-folder 10:21)
  - 1975 Library Administrators Development Program (Box-folder 10:22)
  - 1975-1976 Library Legislation (Box-folder 10:23)
  - 1975 Library Personal Instructional - Contact with Students (Box-folder 10:24)
  - 1972-1975 McFarland, Carl (Box-folder 10:25)
  - 1973-1977 Madison College (Box-folder 10:26)
  - 1976-1983 Miller Center (Center of Public Affairs) (Box-folder 10:27)
  - 1979 National Library Center (Box-folder 10:28)
  - 1976 Peden, William H. (Box-folder 10:29)
  - 1971-1978 Policy-Alderman Library (Box-folder 10:30)
  - 1972-1975 Report on Funds (Box-folder 10:31)
  - 1975-1976 ROTC Affairs Committee (Box-folder 10:32)
  - 1975-1976 Senate ROTC Committee (Box-folder 10:33)
  - 1973-1977 Rotunda Renovation (Box-folder 10:34)
  - 1976-1981 Sesquicentennial (Box-folder 10:35)
  - 1976-1977 Sieg, J. Wallace (Terry) (Box-folder 10:36)
  - 1978-1981 University Development Council (Box-folder 10:37)
  - 1976 University History Officer - Charles E. Moran, Jr. (Box-folder 10:38)
  - 1969-1977 University of Richmond (Box-folder 10:39)
  - 1973-1975 University Transportation Division (Box-folder 10:40)
  - 1977-1980 White House Conference: Library and Information Services (Box-folder 10:41)
  - 1975-1976 Work Study (Box-folder 10:42)
  - 1970-1978 Work Study Expenditures, Summary of (Box-folder 10:43)
  - 1975-1979 Work Study Memos (Box-folder 10:44)
- Series III: Bound Reports
  - 1967-1968 Bound Reports-Library Funds-Departments and Health Education and Welfare (H.E.W.) (Box 11)
  - 1968-1969 Bound Reports-Library Funds-Departments and Health Education and Welfare (H.E.W.) (Box 11)
  - 1963-1964 Bound Reports-Library Funds-1210-1593-B (Box 11)
  - 1964-1965 Bound Reports-Library Funds-A-Z (Box 11)
  - 1965-1966 Bound Reports-Library Funds-1210-1741 (Box 11)
  - 1965-1966 Bound Reports-Library Funds-A-Z (Box 11)
  - 1966-1967 Bound Reports-Library Funds-1210-1785 (Box 11)
  - 1967-1968 Bound Reports-Library Funds-1210-1785 (Box 11)
  - 1964-1965 Bound Reports-Library Funds-Departments (Box 12)
  - 1964-1965 Bound Reports-Library Funds-1210-1241 (Box 12)
  - 1965-1966 Bound Reports-Library Funds-Departments (Box 12)
  - 1963-1964 Bound Reports-Library Funds-A-Z (Box 12)
  - 1966-1967 Bound Reports-Library Funds-Departments (Box 12)
- Series IV: Personnel Records
  - 1968-1980 Personnel-Employee Education (Box-folder 13:1)
  - 1968-1977 Personnel-Employee Identification (Box-folder 13:2)
  - 1968-1974 Personnel-Equal Opportunity (Box-folder 13:3)
  - 1975-1976 Personnel-Equal Opportunity (Box-folder 13:4)
  - 1977 Personnel-Equal Opportunity (Box-folder 13:5)
  - 1978-1979 Personnel-Equal Opportunity- A Self Study (Box-folder 13:6)
  - 1980 Personnel-Equal Opportunity (Box-folder 13:7)
  - 1967-1974 Personnel-Fair Labor Standards Act (Box-folder 13:8)
  - 1969-1972 Personnel-Grievance Procedure (Box-folder 13:9)
  - 1977 Personnel-Half-Time Positions (Box-folder 13:10)
  - 1974-1977 Personnel-Job Qualification Letters-Requests to Fill Vacant Positions (Box-folder 13:11)
  - 1982 Personnel-Job Qualifications (Box-folder 13:12)
  - 1970-1976 Personnel-Job Qualifications-Acquisitions (Box-folder 13:13)
  - 1966 Personnel-Job Qualifications - Administration (Box-folder 13:14)
  - 1974 Personnel-Job Qualifications - Area Collections (Box-folder 13:15)
  - 1976-1977 Personnel-Job Qualifications -Cataloging (Box-folder 13:15)
  - 1972 Personnel-Job Qualifications - Circulation (Box-folder 13:16)
  - 1974 Personnel-Job Qualifications - Clerical Positions (Box-folder 13:17)
  - n.d. Personnel-Job Qualifications - Duplicating Services (Box-folder 13:18)
  - n.d. Personnel-Job Qualifications - Historian (Box-folder 13:19)
  - 1969-1980 Personnel-Hiring Procedure (Box-folder 13:20)
  - 1970 Personnel-Hiring Procedure - Professional (Box-folder 13:21)
  - 1980 Personnel-Job Qualifications - Library Assistant (Box-folder 13:22)
  - 1970-1973 Personnel-Job Qualifications-Manuscripts (Box-folder 13:23)
  - 1976 Personnel-Job Qualifications - Rare Books (Box-folder 13:24)
  - 1969-1977 Personnel-Job Qualifications-Reference (Box-folder 13:25)
  - 1973-1976 Personnel-Job Qualifications-Science and Technology (Box-folder 13:26)
  - 1968-1980 Personnel - Leave (Box-folder 13:27)
  - 1968-1980 Personnel-Merit Increases (Box-folder 13:28)
  - 1972-1980 Personnel-Policy Board (Box-folder 13:29)
  - 1961-1963 Personnel-Positions Established (Box-folder 13:30)
  - 1964 Personnel-Positions Established (Box-folder 13:31)
  - 1965 Personnel-Positions Established (Box-folder 13:32)
  - 1966 Personnel-Positions Established (Box-folder 13:33)
  - 1967 Personnel-Positions Established (Box-folder 13:34)
  - 1968 Personnel-Positions Established (Box-folder 13:35)
  - 1969 Personnel-Positions Established (Box-folder 14:1)
  - 1970 Personnel-Positions Established (Box-folder 14:2)
  - 1971 Personnel-Positions Established (Box-folder 14:3)
  - 1972 Personnel-Positions Established (Box-folder 14:4)
  - 1973 Personnel-Positions Established (Box-folder 14:5)
  - 1975 Personnel-Positions Established (Box-folder 14:6)
  - 1976 Personnel-Positions Established (Box-folder 14:7)
  - 1977-1979 Personnel - Records (Box-folder 14:8)
  - 1968-1977 Personnel-Recruitment - Library Schools (Box-folder 14:9)
  - 1963-1973 Personnel-Request for Reallocation of Position (Box-folder 14:10)
  - 1973-1974 Personnel-Request for Reallocation of Position (Box-folder 14:11)
  - 1975 Personnel-Request for Reallocation of Position (Box-folder 14:12)
  - 1976-1978 Personnel-Request for Reallocation of Position (Box-folder 14:13)
  - 1979-1980 Personnel-Request for Reallocation of Position (Box-folder 14:14)
  - 1975-1977 Personnel-Reorganization of Library Administration (Box-folder 14:15)
  - 1970-1980 Personnel - Recruiting (Box-folder 14:16)
  - 1968-1981 Personnel - Salaries (Box-folder 14:17)
  - 1969-1980 Personnel-Salaries - Hourly PayvRates (Box-folder 14:18)
  - 1971-1975 Personnel-Payroll - Savings Bonds (Box-folder 14:19)
  - 1968-1980 Personnel - Schedules (Box-folder 14:20)
  - 1976 Personnel-Speakers, Entertainment (Box-folder 14:21)
  - 1969-1980 Personnel-Service Awards (Box-folder 14:22)
  - 1969-1980 Personnel-State Classified Procedures (Box-folder 14:23)
  - 1968-1980 Personnel-Student Assistants (Box-folder 14:24)
  - 1969-1979 Personnel-Transfer and Promotions (Box-folder 14:25)
  - 1968 Personnel (Box-folder 14:26)
  - 1969 Personnel (Box-folder 14:27)
  - 1970 Personnel (Box-folder 14:28)
  - 1971 Personnel (Box-folder 14:29)
  - 1972 Personnel (Box-folder 14:30)
  - 1973-1974 Personnel (Box-folder 14:31)
  - 1975-1976 Personnel (Box-folder 14:32)
  - 1977-1979 Personnel (Box-folder 14:33)
  - Restricted
    - 1973-1982 Promotion Review Board (Box-folder 15:1)
    - 1976-1977 Promotion Review Board (Box-folder 15:2)
    - 1977-1978 Promotion Review Board (Box-folder 15:3)
    - 1978-1979 Promotion Review Board (Box-folder 15:4)
    - 1979-1980 Promotion Review Board (Box-folder 15:5)
    - 1980-1981 Promotion Review Board (Box-folder 15:6)